<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Custom Search Movies</title>
  <description>Movies from yts.mx</description>
  <item>
    <title>Beast Mode (2020)</title>
    <description>When Breen Nash accidentally kills his only client and meal ticket, he turns to an ancient herbal extract with the hope that it will resurrect both his client and his career, but soon learns this elixir brings out the worst in those who imbibe, turning them into bloodthirsty, shape-shifting beasts and leaving Breen no recourse but to stop the creatures himself before his own inner beast consumes him.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/beast-mode-2020</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/beast-mode-2020#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 12:34:21 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/0C447AA11D3D8284872F19D1C4B8A6834527E9CD" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Occurrence at Mills Creek (2020)</title>
    <description>Struggling with the guilt of her sister's accidental death, Clara soon begins to succumb to the same strange occurrences that have haunted her family for generations as she uncovers the unsettling truth about her lineage and its dark legacy.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/occurrence-at-mills-creek-2020</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/occurrence-at-mills-creek-2020#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 08:40:43 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/0E6021B13819DEA24276411582ED354BCF2F5217" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Testament of Dr. Mabuse (1933)</title>
    <description>Berlin police inspector Lohmann investigates a case, in which all clues lead to a man, who's in a hospital for mental illnesses for since many years - Dr. Mabuse.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-testament-of-dr-mabuse-1933</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-testament-of-dr-mabuse-1933#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:24:02 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/C670D9F6331780A0DA929440832DF0811D173E00" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Curse of the Demon (1957)</title>
    <description>Dr. John Holden ventures to London to attend a paranormal psychology symposium with the intention to expose devil cult leader Julian Karswell. Holden is a skeptic and does not believe in Karswell's power. Nonetheless, he accepts an invitation to stay at Karswell's estate, along with Joanna Harrington, niece of Holden's confidant who was electrocuted in a bizarre automobile accident. Karswell secretly slips a parchment into Holden's papers that might possibly be a death curse. Recurring strange events finally strike fear into Holden, who believes that his only hope is to pass the parchment back to Karswell to break the demonic curse.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/curse-of-the-demon-1957</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/curse-of-the-demon-1957#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 03:46:24 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/C15693F057C56E779034397498AF58DEB041E146" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Call (2020)</title>
    <description>Two people live in different times. Seo-Yeon lives in the present and Young-Sook lives in the past. One phone call connects the two, and their lives are changed irrevocably.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/call-2020</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/call-2020#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 13:55:06 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/1C1A55E5C8ACF808155C465E91C9B99408473910" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Island of Lost Souls (1932)</title>
    <description>After his ship goes down, Edward Parker is rescued at sea. Parker gets into a fight with Captain Davies of the Apia and the Captain tosses him overboard while making a delivery to the tiny tropical island of Dr. Moreau. Parker discovers that Moreau has good reason to be so secretive on his lonely island. The doctor is a whip-cracking task master to a growing population of his own gruesome human/animal experiments. He does have one prize result, Lota the beautiful panther woman. Parker's fortunes for escape look up after his fiancée Ruth finds him with the help of fearless Captain Donohue. However, when Moreau's tribe of near-humans rises up to rebel, no one is safe...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/island-of-lost-souls-1932</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/island-of-lost-souls-1932#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 11:53:22 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/64568227668380E2181753F64A7EC4057AD8E582" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Skeleton of Mrs. Morales (1960)</title>
    <description>Bizarre movie about a sexually repressed taxidermist who finds solace in his job while his frigid and deformed wife psychologically tortures him because of his devotion to stuffed animals.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/skeleton-of-mrs-morales-1960</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/skeleton-of-mrs-morales-1960#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 02:48:37 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/8DB84E0628DDE634C9EB323E0A786CC1F8270C79" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Faust (1926)</title>
    <description>God and Satan war over earth; to settle things, they wager on the soul of Faust, a learned and prayerful alchemist. During a plague, Faust despairs and burns his books after failing to stop death; Satan sends Mephisto to tempt Faust, first with insight into treating the plague and then with a day's return to youth. Mephisto is clever, timing the end of this 24 hours as Faust embraces the beautiful Duchess of Parma. Faust trades his soul for youth. Some time later, he's bored, and demands on Easter Sunday that Mephisto take him home. Faust promptly sees and falls in love with the beautiful Gretchen, whose liaison with him brings her dishonor. Is there redemption? Who wins the wager?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/faust-1926</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/faust-1926#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 14:04:37 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/07017FDEB5F85DFEF67CA5C27EE8FEC59E3BE588" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Bird with the Crystal Plumage (1970)</title>
    <description>In Italy, the American writer Sam Dalmas witnesses an attempt of murder of the owner of an art gallery, Monica Ranieri, a couple of days before returning home. Inspector Morosini, who is in charge of investigating the three previous murderers of the serial-killer, asks for help to Dalmas and takes his passport. Dalmas decides to stay with his girlfriend Julia and to help the police in the investigation. The killer threatens Dalmas and Julia by phone and the police overhears a strange noise in the tape. Soon the serial killer stalks Julia and Damas. Who might be the killer?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-bird-with-the-crystal-plumage-1970</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-bird-with-the-crystal-plumage-1970#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 10:38:23 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/848D8D6998A1C99A0E5E2988A1670C7047C20A7E" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Monarch (2000)</title>
    <description>Monarch is part fact, part fiction and unfolds around one night when the injured ruler arrives at a manor house closed for the season. Henry is without the power and control of his palace and is vulnerable from those around him, and from his own sanity. Henry left England financially and morally bankrupt; his collection of enemies his only constant. Even today there is a question mark surrounding his burial and possible exhumation.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/monarch-2000</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/monarch-2000#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 01:52:56 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/4B991EF6E30F7B2D9B87F5208D6BA51CB9A2FD91" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Chaar (2014)</title>
    <description>This film is based on four short stories by different writers: "Bateswarer Abodan" by Parasuram, "Porikkha" by Sharadindu Bandyopadhyay, "Kagtarua" by Satyajit Ray and "Dui Bondhu" by Satyajit Ray.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/chaar-2014</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/chaar-2014#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:41:53 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/6E6841D3DEAD4F1CB3397F4F89C7092D4D0DEDF2" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Wolfman's Got Nards (2018)</title>
    <description>This documentary explores the power of cult film told through the lens of The Monster Squad (1987) and the impact it has on fans, cast and crew, and the industry.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/wolfmans-got-nards-2018</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/wolfmans-got-nards-2018#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 17:39:22 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/78D0F2A3308978D405A7ACDA901078F8EF322A1E" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Boulet Brothers' Dragula: Resurrection (2020)</title>
    <description>Follows competitors from all three seasons of the show returning to compete against one another.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-boulet-brothers-dragula-resurrection-2020</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-boulet-brothers-dragula-resurrection-2020#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:01:28 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/9D74682D966176E88D68A16FFD570D421214A900" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Desperate Living (1977)</title>
    <description>A rich housewife murders her husband with the help of her overweight maid, and the two go on the run, ending up in Mortville, a town providing refuge for criminals. They shack up with a lesbian ex-wrestler and her murderess lover, before running into the tyrannical Queen Carlotta, ruler of Mortville...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/desperate-living-1977</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/desperate-living-1977#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 01:38:49 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/5E1433686505A2DC0DFE692BCC0169BDEB33477C" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Vij eller Prästseminariets likvaka (1967)</title>
    <description>Getting lost, wandering home whilst on leave from his seminary, novice monk Khoma stays in the barn of an old woman. A scuffle breaks out. Later, he is summoned to stand and pray over a young dead woman, in the local church, for three nights. It is here that, while in the long, dark nights of the locked doors, the dead regain life, the souls of Hell taunt the young monk to near terrifying insanity, and the test of Faith will be as powerful as the witches, monsters and the mighty demon Viy who haunt his every step and bay for his very soul.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/vij-eller-prastseminariets-likvaka-1967</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/vij-eller-prastseminariets-likvaka-1967#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 01:10:24 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/A471D791136898AF2631FA4786AE22537CEBA578" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Tenebrae (1982)</title>
    <description>With Argento's trademark visual style, linked with one of his more coherent plots, Tenebrae follows a writer who arrives to Rome only to find somebody is using his novels as the inspiration (and, occasionally, the means) of committing murder. As the death toll mounts the police are ever baffled, and the writer becomes more closely linked to the case than is comfortable.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/tenebrae-1982</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/tenebrae-1982#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 02:16:18 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/C6B90950446629828B8A6EB3D265FF104DA7B763" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Trollhunter (2010)</title>
    <description>When bears are found dead in Norway, students from Volda University (Thomas, Johanna and cameraman Kalle) decide to investigate. They stalk the trail of the mysterious hunter Hans, expecting to find an explanation for the killings. The reluctant Hans tries to flee from the youngsters but then agrees to let them film him in action, provided they follow his orders. Soon the trio of students learns that Hans is actually a troll hunter working for a secret government agency. Further, several dangerous trolls have escaped from their territory and Hans is assigned to eliminate them.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/trollhunter-2010</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/trollhunter-2010#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 21:46:15 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/32BA4AE4901090E69BD000A363BE84514F92CD36" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Bhool Bhulaiyaa (2007)</title>
    <description>When U.S.-based Siddharth visits his Indian home town with his new wife, he insists they stay at the ancestral home, laughing off family members' warnings of ghostly goings-on in the mansion. But events soon make him reconsider his beliefs. As unexplained and terrifying occurrences arise, Siddharth calls on his doctor friend to help solve the mystery. What will be the outcome? Will Siddharth's friend be able to solve this riddle?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/bhool-bhulaiyaa-2007</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/bhool-bhulaiyaa-2007#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 12:59:48 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/3865F93EB4392A739D65ECD8EDE178BD22FEC598" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>An American Crime (2007)</title>
    <description>Based on a true story that shocked the nation in 1965, the film recounts one of the most shocking crimes ever committed against a single victim. Sylvia and Jennie Fae Likens, the two daughters of traveling carnival workers are left for an extended stay at the Indianapolis home of single mother Gertrude Baniszewski and her six children. Times are tough, and Gertrude's financial needs cause her to make this arrangement before realizing how the burden will push her unstable nature to a breaking point. What transpires in the next three months is both riveting and horrific.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/an-american-crime-2007</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/an-american-crime-2007#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 18:28:11 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/F64CF40E35BF68A5C7A7D732E3DAB4295F0D3CBF" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Cat and the Canary (1939)</title>
    <description>Ten years have passed since the death of millionaire, Cyrus Norman. Cosby, Cyrus' attorney, has gathered Cyrus' 6 remaining relatives to his New Orleans' mansion for Cyrus' "reading of the will". To the others disappointment, Joyce is the sole heir, but, due to a streak of insanity running in the family, a second will has been made in case Joyce falls victim to it. This puts Joyce in danger. Suddenly, Miss Lu, Cyrus' maid, appears and warns them that the spirits have told her that one of them will die that night. Following this, Hendrick, a prison guard, warns them that, "The Cat", a homicidal maniac has escaped. This sets up Cyrus' relatives with a night filled with murders, mysteries and intrigue.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-cat-and-the-canary-1939</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-cat-and-the-canary-1939#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 03:51:08 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/0668E45A31CF04489F3B2A9F73FADDAB249CAE20" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Who Can Kill a Child? (1976)</title>
    <description>A couple of English tourists rent a boat to visit the fictitious island of Almanzora, just off the southern Spanish coast. When they arrive, they find the town deserted of adults, there's only children who don't speak but stare at them with eerie smiles. They soon discover that all the children of the island have been posessed by a mysterious force or madness which they can pass from one to another, and which makes them attack and murder their elders, who can't defend themselves because nobody dares to kill a child...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/who-can-kill-a-child-1976</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/who-can-kill-a-child-1976#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 05:57:40 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/3BC76B5FBEC09A94C1C94F62124C8A9D0B514AC7" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Mr. Vampire (1985)</title>
    <description>A ghost sucks the life-force out of a one of Uncle Nine's student. The other is slowly turned into a vampire. They halt his transformation by filing down his teeth! The female ghost throws her head around like a boomerang to protect herself. Can Mr. Vampire chase away the Succubus and the hopping ghost and save his two students?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/mr-vampire-1985</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/mr-vampire-1985#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 20:17:52 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/838C0C1F4AEA340247FC13E580738B3262EB6320" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gamera 3: Revenge of Iris (1999)</title>
    <description>This final installment of the recent Gamera trilogy begins with schoolgirl Ayana discovering a large egg in a cave that, according to legend, houses demons. The egg hatches into a small monster, which Ayana decides to raise and quickly develops as psychic bond with. As Ayana's monster, named Iris, grows to adulthood, the flying turtle Gamera begins to take an interest in this new potential threat. Who will be the victor in the final battle, and how much of Japan will be left standing at the end?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/gamera-3-revenge-of-iris-1999</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/gamera-3-revenge-of-iris-1999#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 13:17:19 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/9D8AFBFA94013784C20456BA78FD5171CAF6B625" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Ghost of Yotsuya (1959)</title>
    <description>This classic Japanese horror movie directed by Nobuo Nakagawa is based on an 18th-century masterpiece</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-ghost-of-yotsuya-1959</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-ghost-of-yotsuya-1959#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 01:44:25 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/61EB0F774ACDCD6095F6EDFDA5946DDB566C173B" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Them! (1954)</title>
    <description>In the New Mexico desert, Police Sgt. Ben Peterson and his partner find a child wandering in the desert and sooner they discover that giant ants are attacking the locals. FBI agent Robert Graham teams up with Ben and with the support of Dr. Harold Medford and his daughter Dr. Patricia 'Pat' Medford, they destroy the colony of ants in the middle of the desert. Dr. Harold Medford explains that the atomic testing in 1945 developed the dangerous mutant ants. But they also discover that two queen ants have flown away to Los Angeles and they are starting a huge colony in the underground of the city. When a mother reports that her two children are missing, the team and the army have a lead to follow. Will they arrive in time to save the children and destroy the colony?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/them-1954</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/them-1954#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 15:56:11 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/3B865E2A537D1D9537814CF7A4CEC6EDE4D40992" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Bad Seed (1956)</title>
    <description>Christine Penmark seems to have it all: a lovely home, a loving husband and the most "perfect" daughter in the world. But since childhood, Christine has suffered from the most terrible recurring nightmare. And her "perfect" daughter's accomplishments include lying, theft and possibly much, much worse. Only Christine knows the truth about her daughter and only Christine's father knows the truth about her nightmare.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-bad-seed-1956</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-bad-seed-1956#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 16:35:45 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/51864B9EA4358562EB3353E71C014862A5C0EE1F" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Woman in Black (1989)</title>
    <description>When a friendless old widow dies in the seaside town of Crythin, a young solicitor is sent by his firm to settle the estate. The lawyer finds the townspeople reluctant to talk about or go near the woman's dreary home and no one will explain or even acknowledge the menacing woman in black he keeps seeing. Ignoring the towns-people's cryptic warnings, he goes to the house where he discovers its horrible history and becomes ensnared in its even more horrible legacy.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-woman-in-black-1989</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-woman-in-black-1989#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 15:09:46 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/2FE87AEDD84A44D40E48C234D9A165A0988E99FD" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Cremator (1969)</title>
    <description>Czech Karel Kopfrkingl enjoys his job at a crematorium in the late 1930s. He likes reading the Tibetan book of the dead, and espouses the view that cremation relieves earthly suffering. At a reception, he meets Reineke, with whom he fought for Austria in the first World War. Reineke convinces Kopfrkingl to emphasize his supposedly German heritage, including sending his timid son to the German school. Reineke then suggests that Kopfrkingl's half-Jewish wife is holding back his advancement in his job.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-cremator-1969</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-cremator-1969#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 18:02:37 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/E73495C27537DAF57AF7D3012AF6019F2B8E40C8" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Memories (1995)</title>
    <description>"Memories" is made up of three separate science-fiction stories. In the first, "Magnetic Rose," four space travelers are drawn into an abandoned spaceship that contains a world created by one woman's memories. In "Stink Bomb," a young lab assistant accidentally transforms himself into a human biological weapon set on a direct course for Tôkyô. The final episode, "Cannon Fodder," depicts a day in the life of a city whose entire purpose is the firing of cannons at an unseen enemy.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/memories-1995</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/memories-1995#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 02:22:52 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/AD7BEFC6D823579AB18F93E9B177D1174246184B" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Big Shave (1967)</title>
    <description>This short film is a metaphor for the Vietnam War. A man walks into a meticulously clean and sterile bathroom, concentrating on the polished porcelain and shiny metal motif. He then proceeds to shave. When his face is clean, however, he only continues to shave until he pierces through his skin. Blood covers him and falls around him, the red contrasting the perfect spotlessness of the bathroom.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-big-shave-1967</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-big-shave-1967#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 13:35:10 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/E807A8C9B72A9A0D2E61EE395FDA221B18343455" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Vampyr (1932)</title>
    <description>Allan Gray arrives late in the evening to a secluded riverside inn in the hamlet of Courtempierre. An old man enters his room, puts a sealed parcel on the table, blurts out that some woman mustn't die, and disappears. Gray senses in this a call for help. He puts the parcel in his pocket, and goes out. Eerie shadows lead him into an old house, where he encounters a weird village doctor. The doctor receives a bottle of poison from a strange, old woman. Through the window of an old castle Gray recognizes the old man from the inn. A shadow shoots the man, who drops dead. Inside the house Gray finds his two daughters, Gisèle and Léone, and some servants. He opens the parcel, and finds an old book about vampires. Léone is seriously ill after being bitten by a vampire. Instead of helping her, the village doctor places the bottle of poison at her bedside table, and then abducts her sister Gisèle. An old servant starts reading the old book, and finds out that the vampire in Courtempierre is a ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/vampyr-1932</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/vampyr-1932#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 13:26:37 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/50A3FD8656F84F8B63365D15C045006CFF9E3D42" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Morgiana (1972)</title>
    <description>Klara and Viktoria are sisters. Their father dies, leaving most of his property to Klara. When Klara becomes involved with a man that her sister loves, Viktoria begins to plot her murder.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/morgiana-1972</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/morgiana-1972#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 21:44:20 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/159ECA5AB639C3CB638115D8EBEA39B088EE8FA8" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Thesis (1996)</title>
    <description>Why is death and violence so fascinating? Is it morally correct to show violence in movies? If so, is there a limit to what we should show? That's the subject of Ángela's examination paper. She is a young student at a film school in Madrid. Together with the student Chema (who is totally obsessed with violent movies) they find a snuff movie in which a young girl is tortured and killed. Soon they discover that the girl was a former student at their school...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/thesis-1996</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/thesis-1996#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 03:20:58 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/A7E5A2599F4E0871A86CE9144F82813F5FAC0174" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Witchhammer (1970)</title>
    <description>The time is the seventeenth century. The beggar Maryna Schuchová hides the Host in her scarf at the Communion. She admits to the parish priest Schmidt that she intended to give it to the midwife Groerová to heal her ailing cow. The young priest declares her a witch and convinces the Sumperk countess De Galle to summon the inquisitor Boblig from Edelstadt. This failed student of law sees the offer as a great opportunity. He uses torture and threats to force the women from the to testify to their meetings with the devil and learn by heart the lies he has made up for the inquisition tribunal. Boblig accuses the wealthy burghers of witchcraft as well, and so wants to seize their possessions.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/witchhammer-1970</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/witchhammer-1970#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 15:10:11 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/B277767C98CF1A6B15B987F9C76DE167E499429E" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Hidden (1987)</title>
    <description>An alien parasite with the ability to possess human bodies goes on a violent crime spree in LA, committing dozens of murders and robberies. In pursuit of the extraterrestrial criminal is an FBI agent, and the local officer investigating the rash of violence. As they close in on the vicious intruder, the city faces a brutal threat like no other it has ever encountered.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-hidden-1987</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-hidden-1987#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 11:58:52 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/FF82844ED47658F320D9618C128B0583939B02EB" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Hourglass Sanatorium (1973)</title>
    <description>The film depicts its protagonist, Joseph (Jan Nowicki), traveling through a dream-like world, taking a dilapidated train to visit his dying father in a sanatorium. When he arrives at the hospital, he finds the entire facility is going to ruin and no one seems to be in charge, or even caring for the patients. Time appears to behave in unpredictable ways, reanimating the past in an elaborate artificial caprice.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-hourglass-sanatorium-1973</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-hourglass-sanatorium-1973#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 10:23:11 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/3743D2C5918B2ADB0A591785AE2F557022D73C04" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Empire of Passion (1978)</title>
    <description>A young man has an affair with an older woman. He is very jealous of her husband and decides that they should kill him. One night, after the husband had plenty of sake to drink and was in bed, they strangle him and dump his body down a well. To avert any suspicions, she pretends her husband has gone off to Tokyo to work. For three years the wife and her lover secretly see each other. Finally, suspicions become very strong and people begin to gossip. To make matters worse, her husband's ghost begins to haunt her and the law arrives to investigate her husband's disappearance.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/empire-of-passion-1978</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/empire-of-passion-1978#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 16:47:34 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/F991DEA5CADC6C8E257EF6772847F527130E60A3" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Marshland (2014)</title>
    <description>1980. In a little town close to Coto of Doñana (Andalusia, south to Spain), two teen girls have disappeared. The father of one of the girls, who have connections with important people in the forces of the law, gets that two police detectives of homicides from Madrid are assigned to the mission to find the girls if they are alive, or find the assassin if they appear died. The detectives are Pedro Suárez and Juan Robles. While that Suárez is a young, taciturn and circumspect agent in a Spain that it tries to find a new identity as democratic country after General Franco's death in 1975, Robles is a veteran, funny and expeditious agent, with a mysterious past as alleged member of Franco's Armed Police dismantled in 1978. Unable to reconcile one with each other, Suárez and Robles find trapped by the hostile environment of a place where the old Franco's methods and customs still alive, and where they two aren't welcome. When the girls appears died, the following investigation move the cops...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/marshland-2014</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/marshland-2014#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 02:52:53 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/B65E6E5BE24FF3E0855FE56DAA36798B9D73815A" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>November (2017)</title>
    <description>"November" is based on Estonian novel "Rehepapp" by Andrus Kivirähk, a bestseller of the last twenty years. The film is a mixture of magic, black humor and romantic love. The story is set in a pagan Estonian village where werewolves, the plague, and spirits roam. The villagers' main problem is how to survive the cold, dark winter. And, to that aim, nothing is taboo. People steal from each other, from their German manor lords, and from spirits, the devil, and Christ. To guard their souls, they'll give them away to thieving creatures made of wood and metal called kratts, who help their masters by stealing more. They steal even if their barns are already overflowing. Stealing is an obsession that makes the villagers more and more like the soulless creatures they command, the kratts. The main character of the film is a young farm girl named Liina who is hopelessly and forlornly in love with a village boy named Hans. Her longing makes the girl become a werewolf and jump into an ice-cold ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/november-2017</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/november-2017#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 19:26:26 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/9BCB870A754D90DAD198A0217E82689436F7F34F" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Bacurau (2019)</title>
    <description>Bacurau, a small settlement in Brazil's remote backcountry, is shaken by the death of its elderly matriarch. But something strange is happening in the village, and there's little time for mourning. The water supply has been cut off, animals are stampeding through the streets, and empty coffins are turning up on the roadside. One morning, the villagers wake up to find their home has disappeared from satellite maps completely. Under threat from an unknown enemy, Bacurau braces itself for a bloody, brutal fight for survival.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/bacurau-2019</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/bacurau-2019#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 01:20:45 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/6656E191533D3FCFC7546DE83923C73746FBDDBD" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night (2014)</title>
    <description>An Iranian Vampire Western, shot in black&amp;white and with a killer soundtrack... it's a love story about two tortured souls in a desolate Iranian Ghost-town called 'Bad City', where a lonely vampire is stalking the towns most depraved denizens.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/a-girl-walks-home-alone-at-night-2014</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/a-girl-walks-home-alone-at-night-2014#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 12:22:43 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/D1446DBA9E320DBDA272DC97F2266F72304228EE" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Eyes Without a Face (1960)</title>
    <description>After causing an accident that left his daughter Christiane severely disfigured, the brilliant surgeon Dr. Génessier works tirelessly to give the girl a new face. He does so however by kidnapping young women and attempting face transplants. He has been woefully unsuccessful to date. The doctor's world begins to collapse around him when his daughter realizes just what he has been doing.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/eyes-without-a-face-1960</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/eyes-without-a-face-1960#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 20:42:32 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/67750441C5FEA882AAF31DC95C1D91C25C55CE9F" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Mientras duermes (2011)</title>
    <description>Apartment concierge Cesar (Luis Tosar) is a miserable person who believes he was born without the ability to be happy. As a result, he decides his mission is to make life hell for everyone around him. A majority of the tenants are easy to agitate, but Clara (Marta Etura) proves to be harder than the most. So Cesar goes to creepy extremes to make this young woman mentally break down. Things get even more complicated in this twisted relationship when her boyfriend, Marcos (Alberto San Juan), shows up.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/mientras-duermes-2011</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/mientras-duermes-2011#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 03:32:20 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/ECC4ED1C041F9390C1556ADEB751386406042922" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Black Cat (1968)</title>
    <description>A woman and her daughter-in-law are raped and murdered by samurais during the time of civil war. Afterwards, a series of samurai returning from the war through that area are found mysteriously dead with their throats torn out. The governor calls in a wild and fierce young hero, to quell what is evidently a ghost. He encounters the two beautiful women, in an eerie, beautiful scene. After spiritual purification, he meets the demon in a thrilling fight.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/black-cat-1968</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/black-cat-1968#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 10:50:54 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/E83E64C3CA6B76174A0479565A34785EBF5EDF13" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Timecrimes (2007)</title>
    <description>Hector is an ordinary man who's moving to a new house with his wife. One evening, while he's looking through his binoculars, he sees a naked girl in the woods. He decides to go there just to find that same girl laying on a rock. Suddenly, a man with a pink bandage covering his face, stabs Hector in his arm with scissors...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/timecrimes-2007</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/timecrimes-2007#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 14:29:19 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/BF659645C69D8EA5BE7EF71EA6C579D4626099E6" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Eight Immortals Restaurant: The Untold Story (1993)</title>
    <description>In 1978 in Hong Kong, a grisly murder takes place. Eight years later, on a Macao beach, kids discover the severed hands of a fresh victim. A squadron of coarse, happy-go-lucky cops investigate, and suspicion falls on Wong Chi Hang, the new owner of Eight Immortals Restaurant, which serves delicious pork bao. The hands belong to the missing mother of the restaurant's former owner; he and his family have disappeared; staff at the restaurant continue to go missing; and, Wong can't produce a signed bill of sale: but there's no evidence. The police arrest Wong and try to torture him into a confession. Can they make him talk? And what was in those pork bao?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-eight-immortals-restaurant-the-untold-story-1993</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-eight-immortals-restaurant-the-untold-story-1993#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 03:11:29 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/912BD6B68049BA4E9EAECFF92A38B604F3EF94ED" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Onibaba (1964)</title>
    <description>In the Fourteenth Century, during a civil war in Japan, a middle-aged woman and her daughter-in-law survive in a hut in a field of reed killing warriors and soldiers to trade their possessions for food. When their neighbor Hachi defects from the war and returns home, they learn that their son and husband Kichi died while stealing supplies from farmers. Soon Hachi seduces the young widow and she sneaks out of her hut every night to have sex with him. When the older woman finds the affair of her daughter-in-law, she pleads with Hachi to leave the young woman with her since she would not be able to kill the warriors without her help. However, Hachi ignores her request and continues to meet the young woman. When a samurai wearing a demon mask stumbles upon the older woman at her hut asking her to guide him out of the field, she lures him and he falls in the pit where she drops the bodies of her victims. She climbs down the hole to take his possessions and his mask, and she finds he is a ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/onibaba-1964</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/onibaba-1964#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 05:51:34 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/069652BFE1B5A07C8B6153A4A2264DC6258AC037" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Kim Bok-nam salinsageonui jeonmal (2010)</title>
    <description>Hae-won is a beautiful single woman in her thirties who works at a bank in the Seoul city. She leads a busy life until she becomes a witness to an attempted murder case, and at the same time, things get complicated at work. When things get out of hand she is forced to take a vacation so she heads for 'Moodo', a small undeveloped island, where she had once visited to see her grandparents. And where she had befriended a girl named Bok-nam who stills writes to Hae-won asking her to visit despite the fact that Hae-won never bothered to reply. Upon arriving at the island, Hae-won is shocked to see everyone treating Bok-nam like a slave. As practically the only young woman on the island, she is a plaything for all the men and a free laborer for the women. Sick of all the inhumane treatment, Bok-nam had tried to escape the island several times in the past but had failed each time. She begs Hae-won to help her escape the place, but Hae-won remains indifferent not wanting to be involved in ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/kim-bok-nam-salinsageonui-jeonmal-2010</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/kim-bok-nam-salinsageonui-jeonmal-2010#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 21:15:59 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/CB01A674492175C2F1037CDFC80E7A8FA03A2FF4" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Tetsuo: The Iron Man (1989)</title>
    <description>Mad with pain by the festering wound in his thigh, an extreme sado-sexual "Metal Fetishist" dashes out into the street, and is accidentally hit by the car of a white-collar worker and his girlfriend. But, strangely, instead of dying, the salaryman finds himself before a mysterious and agonisingly majestic transformation--one that twists and bends the pliable human flesh, inextricably intertwining it with the strong and cold iron. Now, there is no turning back, and nothing can stand in the way of the glorious final mutation. Is this the beginning of a new era?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/tetsuo-the-iron-man-1989</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/tetsuo-the-iron-man-1989#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 15:15:22 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/216783D7B5F435E07E344D3BD339AC44A9D9D630" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>