<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Academy Award-winning Movies</title>
  <description>Academy Award-winning Movies from yts.mx</description>
  <item>
    <title>Parasite (2019)</title>
    <description>The Kims - mother and father Chung-sook and Ki-taek, and their young adult offspring, son Ki-woo and daughter Ki-jung - are a poor family living in a shabby and cramped half basement apartment in a busy lower working class commercial district of Seoul. Without even knowing it, they, especially Mr. and Mrs. Kim, literally smell of poverty. Often as a collective, they perpetrate minor scams to get by, and even when they have jobs, they do the minimum work required. Ki-woo is the one who has dreams of getting out of poverty by one day going to university. Despite not having that university education, Ki-woo is chosen by his university student friend Min, who is leaving to go to school, to take over his tutoring job to Park Da-hye, who Min plans to date once he returns to Seoul and she herself is in university. The Parks are a wealthy family who for four years have lived in their modernistic house designed by and the former residence of famed architect Namgoong. While Mr. and Mrs. Park ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/parasite-2019</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/parasite-2019#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 16:03:06 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/CE6D2A6BBC439A8F6B94B23BA63B04164400FE3B" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>No Country for Old Men (2007)</title>
    <description>In rural Texas, welder and hunter Llewelyn Moss (Josh Brolin) discovers the remains of several drug runners who have all killed each other in an exchange gone violently wrong. Rather than report the discovery to the police, Moss decides to simply take the two million dollars present for himself. This puts the psychopathic killer, Anton Chigurh (Javier Bardem), on his trail as he dispassionately murders nearly every rival, bystander and even employer in his pursuit of his quarry and the money. As Moss desperately attempts to keep one step ahead, the blood from this hunt begins to flow behind him with relentlessly growing intensity as Chigurh closes in. Meanwhile, the laconic Sheriff Ed Tom Bell (Tommy Lee Jones) blithely oversees the investigation even as he struggles to face the sheer enormity of the crimes he is attempting to thwart.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/no-country-for-old-men-2007</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/no-country-for-old-men-2007#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:24:59 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/D97CB718557D7EFDA484014D8F0158C68C8BFA59" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>12 Years a Slave (2013)</title>
    <description>Based on an incredible true story of one man's fight for survival and freedom. In the pre-Civil War United States, Solomon Northup, a free black man from upstate New York, is abducted and sold into slavery. Facing cruelty personified by a malevolent slave owner, as well as unexpected kindnesses, Solomon struggles not only to stay alive, but to retain his dignity. In the twelfth year of his unforgettable odyssey, Solomon's chance meeting with a Canadian abolitionist will forever alter his life.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/12-years-a-slave-2013</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/12-years-a-slave-2013#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 20:46:15 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/AAD050EE1BB22E196939547B134535824DABF0CE" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Slumdog Millionaire (2008)</title>
    <description>The story of Jamal Malik, an 18 year-old orphan from the slums of Mumbai, who is about to experience the biggest day of his life. With the whole nation watching, he is just one question away from winning a staggering 20 million rupees on India's Kaun Banega Crorepati? (2000) (Who Wants To Be A Millionaire?) But when the show breaks for the night, police arrest him on suspicion of cheating; how could a street kid know so much? Desperate to prove his innocence, Jamal tells the story of his life in the slum where he and his brother grew up, of their adventures together on the road, of vicious encounters with local gangs, and of Latika, the girl he loved and lost. Each chapter of his story reveals the key to the answer to one of the game show's questions. Each chapter of Jamal's increasingly layered story reveals where he learned the answers to the show's seemingly impossible quizzes. But one question remains a mystery: what is this young man with no apparent desire for riches really ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/slumdog-millionaire-2008</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/slumdog-millionaire-2008#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:30:30 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/8689EB06DD5F744B7937BED04C3F8B9B44BBCF04" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Artist (2011)</title>
    <description>Outside a movie premiere, enthusiastic fan Peppy Miller literally bumps into the swashbuckling hero of the silent film, George Valentin. The star reacts graciously and Peppy plants a kiss on his cheek as they are surrounded by photographers. The headlines demand: "Who's That Girl?" and Peppy is inspired to audition for a dancing bit-part at the studio. However as Peppy slowly rises through the industry, the introduction of talking-pictures turns Valentin's world upside-down.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-artist-2011</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-artist-2011#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:04:07 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/37FF3345E5EA5FD3B5A39954F89038E28A264F0F" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The King's Speech (2010)</title>
    <description>Britain's Prince Albert (Colin Firth) must ascend the throne as King George VI, but he has a speech impediment. Knowing that the country needs her husband to be able to communicate effectively, Elizabeth (Helena Bonham Carter) hires Lionel Logue (Geoffrey Rush), an Australian actor and speech therapist, to help him overcome his stammer. An extraordinary friendship develops between the two men, as Logue uses unconventional means to teach the monarch how to speak with confidence.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-kings-speech-2010</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-kings-speech-2010#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:51:45 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/7535410CF484960804EB9906DBAD7D18386BBE4E" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Argo (2012)</title>
    <description>In 1979, the American embassy in Iran was invaded by Iranian revolutionaries and several Americans were taken hostage. However, six managed to escape to the official residence of the Canadian Ambassador and the CIA was ordered to get them out of the country. With few options, exfiltration expert Tony Mendez devised a daring plan: create a phony Canadian film project looking to shoot in Iran and smuggle the Americans out as its production crew. With the help of some trusted Hollywood contacts, Mendez created the ruse and proceeded to Iran as its associate producer. However, time was running out with the Iranian security forces closing in on the truth while both his charges and the White House had grave doubts about the operation themselves.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/argo-2012</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/argo-2012#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 21:33:16 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/32DDAA8C1BBC4C78339199FAB88CF7EBFA0C9720" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Birdman or (2014)</title>
    <description>Actor Riggan Thomson is most famous for his movie role from over twenty years ago of the comic book superhero Birdman in the blockbuster movie of the same name and its two equally popular sequels. His association with the role took over his life, where Birdman is more renowned than "Riggan Thomson" the actor. Now past middle age, Riggan is trying to establish himself as a true artist by writing, directing, starring in and co-producing with his best friend Jake what is his Broadway debut, an adaptation of Raymond Carver's story, What We Talk About When We Talk About Love. He is staking his name, what little artistic reputation that comes with that name and his life savings on the project, and as such will do anything needed to make the play a success. As he and Jake go through the process of the previews toward opening night, Riggan runs into several issues: needing to find a replacement for the integral supporting male role the night before the first preview; hiring the talented ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/birdman-or-2014</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/birdman-or-2014#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 21:59:59 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/2302ECAB74207E7831055400563A61AA23025FE5" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Spotlight (2015)</title>
    <description>When the Boston Globe's tenacious "Spotlight" team of reporters delves into allegations of abuse in the Catholic Church, their year-long investigation uncovers a decades-long cover-up at the highest levels of Boston's religious, legal, and government establishment, touching off a wave of revelations around the world.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/spotlight-2015</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/spotlight-2015#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 12:50:22 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/D865DF5BB761D4C976265DF922AC679D39130B4E" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Shape of Water (2017)</title>
    <description>From master storyteller Guillermo del Toro comes THE SHAPE OF WATER, an otherworldly fable set against the backdrop of Cold War era America circa 1962. In the hidden high-security government laboratory where she works, lonely Elisa (Sally Hawkins) is trapped in a life of isolation. Elisa's life is changed forever when she and co-worker Zelda (Octavia Spencer) discover a secret classified experiment. Rounding out the cast are Michael Shannon, Richard Jenkins, Michael Stuhlbarg, and Doug Jones.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-shape-of-water-2017</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-shape-of-water-2017#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 20:26:45 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/1B74773D24E47A928F57736DDB529AA7CBEBE3A3" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Green Book (2018)</title>
    <description>In 1962, Tony "Tony Lip" Vallelonga, a tough bouncer, is looking for work when his nightclub is closed for renovations. The most promising offer turns out to be the driver for the African-American classical pianist Don Shirley for a concert tour into the Deep South states. Although hardly enthused at working for a black man, Tony accepts the job and they begin their trek armed with The Negro Motorist Green Book, a travel guide for safe travel through America's racial segregation. Together, the snobbishly erudite pianist and the crudely practical bouncer can barely get along with their clashing attitudes to life and ideals. However, as the disparate pair witness and endure America's appalling injustices on the road, they find a newfound respect for each other's talents and start to face them together. In doing so, they would nurture a friendship and understanding that would change both their lives.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/green-book-2018</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/green-book-2018#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 12:58:00 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/696CDF86B1402B7094719190269E76703786A390" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Moonlight (2016)</title>
    <description>Three time periods - young adolescence, mid-teen and young adult - in the life of black-American Chiron is presented. When a child, Chiron lives with his single, crack addict mother Paula in a crime ridden neighborhood in Miami. Chiron is a shy, withdrawn child largely due to his small size and being neglected by his mother, who is more concerned about getting her fixes and satisfying her carnal needs than taking care of him. Because of these issues, Chiron is bullied, the slurs hurled at him which he doesn't understand beyond knowing that they are meant to be hurtful. Besides his same aged Cuban-American friend Kevin, Chiron is given what little guidance he has in life from a neighborhood drug dealer named Juan, who can see that he is neglected, and Juan's caring girlfriend Teresa, whose home acts as a sanctuary away from the bullies and away from Paula's abuse. With this childhood as a foundation, Chiron may have a predetermined path in life, one that will only be magnified in terms...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/moonlight-2016</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/moonlight-2016#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 16:35:05 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/CBE24E29CD49AB2923DC927B467AA594B73A119A" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Schindler's List (1993)</title>
    <description>Oskar Schindler is a vain and greedy German businessman who becomes an unlikely humanitarian amid the barbaric German Nazi reign when he feels compelled to turn his factory into a refuge for Jews. Based on the true story of Oskar Schindler who managed to save about 1100 Jews from being gassed at the Auschwitz concentration camp, it is a testament to the good in all of us.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/schindlers-list-1993</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/schindlers-list-1993#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:16:11 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/F64C844C39FCD6A5F9157884E97296F7019DB83B" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Forrest Gump (1994)</title>
    <description>Forrest Gump is a simple man with a low I.Q. but good intentions. He is running through childhood with his best and only friend Jenny. His 'mama' teaches him the ways of life and leaves him to choose his destiny. Forrest joins the army for service in Vietnam, finding new friends called Dan and Bubba, he wins medals, creates a famous shrimp fishing fleet, inspires people to jog, starts a ping-pong craze, creates the smiley, writes bumper stickers and songs, donates to people and meets the president several times. However, this is all irrelevant to Forrest who can only think of his childhood sweetheart Jenny Curran, who has messed up her life. Although in the end all he wants to prove is that anyone can love anyone.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/forrest-gump-1994</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/forrest-gump-1994#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 23:30:05 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/FEE625A78CB2057CE7845AA66E95F60D43EA8AB0" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>You Can't Take It with You (1938)</title>
    <description>The stenographer Alice Sycamore is in love with her boss Tony Kirby, who is the vice-president of the powerful company owned by his greedy father Anthony P. Kirby. Kirby Sr. is dealing a monopoly in the trade of weapons, and needs to buy one last house in a twelve block area owned by Alice's grandparent Martin Vanderhof. However, Martin is the patriarch of an anarchic and eccentric family where the members do not care for money but for having fun and making friends. When Tony proposes Alice, she states that it would be mandatory to introduce her simple and lunatic family to the snobbish Kirbys, and Tony decides to visit Alice with his parents one day before the scheduled. There is an inevitable clash of classes and lifestyles, the Kirbys spurn the Sycamores and Alice breaks with Tony, changing the lives of the Kirby family.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/you-cant-take-it-with-you-1938</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/you-cant-take-it-with-you-1938#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 05:25:40 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/98D643642C940316D49997A37A82E47D6EDFAF4A" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Wings (1927)</title>
    <description>Two young men from the same town but different social classes end up as fighter pilots in WW1. Jack Preston is a keen auto mechanic, building and modifying cars. David Armstrong comes from a wealthy family. They are both in love with the same woman, Sylvia. Her heart belongs to David but she doesn't let Jack know and plays along with his infatuation. Meanwhile, Jack's neighbour, Mary, is deeply in love with him but he just views her as a friend. WW1 interrupts the romantic entanglements as Jack and David enlist in the US Army Air Service (Air Service of the AEF at the time). They are initially bitter enemies, due to them both vying for Sylvia's affections. Over time, however, they become very good friends. They are both posted to the same fighter squadron in France, where being a fighter pilot means every day could easily be your last.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/wings-1927</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/wings-1927#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 04:08:30 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/73E4E67FE5C8175F770F2C44308F8268A490B827" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>My Fair Lady (1964)</title>
    <description>Pompous phonetics Professor Henry Higgins (Sir Rex Harrison) is so sure of his abilities that he takes it upon himself to transform a Cockney working-class girl into someone who can pass for a cultured member of high society. His subject turns out to be the lovely Eliza Doolittle (Audrey Hepburn), who agrees to speech lessons to improve her job prospects. Higgins and Eliza clash, then form an unlikely bond, one that is threatened by aristocratic suitor Freddy Eynsford-Hill (Jeremy Brett).</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/my-fair-lady-1964</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/my-fair-lady-1964#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 20:10:24 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/A2C147BB514DE8BA76D37CFD7090BD50343D085C" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Rebecca (1940)</title>
    <description>A shy lady's companion, staying in Monte Carlo with her stuffy employer, meets the wealthy Maxim de Winter (Sir Laurence Olivier). She and Max fall in love, marry, and return to Manderley, his large country estate in Cornwall. Max is still troubled by the death of his first wife, Rebecca, in a boating accident the year before. The second Mrs. de Winter (Joan Fontaine) clashes with the housekeeper, Mrs. Danvers (Dame Judith Anderson), and discovers that Rebecca still has a strange hold on everyone at Manderley.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/rebecca-1940</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/rebecca-1940#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 11:28:37 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/B55EF3BCBEE886FE3B831BC617EE117A66BD153A" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Marty (1955)</title>
    <description>Stuck as the last of six children at home with an overbearing Italian mother, the only child still unmarried, 34 year old socially awkward Bronx butcher Marty faces middle age with no prospects of marriage, and he faces permanent bachelorhood. But when he is goaded by his mother into going to the Stardust Ballroom one Saturday night, Marty unexpectedly meets Clara, a lonely teacher. Suddenly, Marty's future seems bright.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/marty-1955</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/marty-1955#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:02:40 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/48DA8D719BE203298D35B319F1B7A17BC2467FEA" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>West Side Story (1961)</title>
    <description>West Side Story is the award-winning adaptation of the classic romantic tragedy "Romeo and Juliet". The feuding families become two warring New York City gangs--the white Jets led by Riff and the Latino Sharks, led by Bernardo. Their hatred escalates to a point where neither can coexist with any form of understanding. But when Riff's best friend (and former Jet) Tony and Bernardo's younger sister Maria meet at a dance, no one can do anything to stop their love. Maria and Tony begin meeting in secret, planning to run away. Then the Sharks and Jets plan a rumble under the highway--whoever wins gains control of the streets. Maria sends Tony to stop it, hoping it can end the violence. It goes terribly wrong, and before the lovers know what's happened, tragedy strikes and doesn't stop until the climactic and heartbreaking ending.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/west-side-story-1961</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/west-side-story-1961#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 19:35:30 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/2DA84E4B05675B192A869C0BC851F9F3337F8034" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>On the Waterfront (1954)</title>
    <description>Terry Malloy dreams about being a prize fighter, while tending his pigeons and running errands at the docks for Johnny Friendly, the corrupt boss of the dockers union. Terry witnesses a murder by two of Johnny's thugs, and later meets the dead man's sister and feels responsible for his death. She introduces him to Father Barry, who tries to force him to provide information for the courts that will smash the dock racketeers.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/on-the-waterfront-1954</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/on-the-waterfront-1954#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 03:26:29 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/60B20F328C117825CC988A366C44C63B73AE9F7B" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Mutiny on the Bounty (1935)</title>
    <description>Midshipman Roger Byam joins Captain Bligh and Fletcher Christian aboard HMS Bounty for a voyage to Tahiti. Bligh proves to be a brutal tyrant and, after six pleasant months on Tahiti, Christian leads the crew to mutiny on the homeward voyage. Even though Byam takes no part in the mutiny, he must defend himself against charges that he supported Christian.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/mutiny-on-the-bounty-1935</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/mutiny-on-the-bounty-1935#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 08:17:23 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/5F78A535953C1CDBDD698ADE9EC55E34A6879E67" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Mrs. Miniver (1942)</title>
    <description>The Minivers, an English "middle-class" family experience life in the first months of World War II. While dodging bombs, the Minivers' son courts Lady Beldon's granddaughter. A rose is named after Mrs. Miniver and entered in the competition against Lady Beldon's rose.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/mrs-miniver-1942</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/mrs-miniver-1942#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 23:17:28 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/6B3A0D0AC185A47B48E970B3C21F5246EFE36175" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Tom Jones (1963)</title>
    <description>In eighteenth-century England, "first cousins" Tom Jones and Master Blifil grew up together in privilege in the western countryside, but could not be more different in nature. Tom, the bastard son of one of Squire Allworthy's servants Jenny Jones and the local barber Partridge, was raised by virtuous Allworthy as his own after he sent Jenny away. Tom is randy, chasing anything in a skirt, he's having a sexual relationship on the sly with Molly Seagrim, the peasant daughter of Allworthy's gamekeeper. Tom is nonetheless kind-hearted and good-natured, he who is willing to defend that and those in which he believes. Blifil, on the other hand, is dour, and although outwardly pious, is cold-hearted and vengeful. Despite his randiness, Tom eventually falls in love with Sophie Western, who has just returned to the area after a few years abroad. Despite Sophie's love for Tom, Squire Western and his spinster sister would rather see Sophie marry Blifil rather than a bastard, who Western ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/tom-jones-1963</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/tom-jones-1963#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 09:18:38 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/2B36D0C182F51C650BFF68BCCB60FDD115132C41" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Lost Weekend (1945)</title>
    <description>Don Birnam, long-time alcoholic, has been "on the wagon" for ten days and seems to be over the worst; but his craving has just become more insidious. Evading a country weekend planned by his brother Wick and girlfriend Helen, he begins a four-day bender. In flashbacks we see past events, all gone wrong because of the bottle. But this bout looks like being his last...one way or the other.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-lost-weekend-1945</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-lost-weekend-1945#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 22:10:51 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/5FD38ABBAF8023DFC49D93DB8F2CC3E913A9D145" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Lawrence of Arabia (1962)</title>
    <description>Due to his knowledge of the native Bedouin tribes, British Lieutenant T.E. Lawrence is sent to Arabia to find Prince Faisal and serve as a liaison between the Arabs and the British in their fight against the Turks. With the aid of native Sherif Ali, Lawrence rebels against the orders of his superior officer and strikes out on a daring camel journey across the harsh desert to attack a well-guarded Turkish port.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/lawrence-of-arabia-1962</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/lawrence-of-arabia-1962#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:41:44 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/93F8F3E1D5EEC00B51BE5EB9A5FD3D99244394DD" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>It Happened One Night (1934)</title>
    <description>Ellie Andrews has just tied the knot with society aviator King Westley when she is whisked away to her father's yacht and out of King's clutches. Ellie jumps ship and eventually winds up on a bus headed back to her husband. Reluctantly she must accept the help of out-of- work reporter Peter Warne. Actually, Warne doesn't give her any choice: either she sticks with him until he gets her back to her husband, or he'll blow the whistle on Ellie to her father. Either way, Peter gets what (he thinks!) he wants .... a really juicy newspaper story.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/it-happened-one-night-1934</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/it-happened-one-night-1934#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:21:00 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/DD6623EAAB97E1A784EA43095A922057A89E7439" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>How Green Was My Valley (1941)</title>
    <description>Life is hard in a Welsh mining town and no less so for the Morgan family. Seen through the eyes of the family's youngest, Huw, we learn of the family's trials and tribulations. Family patriarch Gwilym and his older sons work in the mines, dangerous and unhealthy as it is. Gwilym has greater hopes for his youngest son, but Huw has his own ideas on how to honor his father. Daughter Angharad is the most beautiful girl in the valley and is very much in love with Mr. Gruffydd, who isn't sure he can provide her the life she deserves. Times are hard and good men find themselves out of work and exploited by unseen mine owners.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/how-green-was-my-valley-1941</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/how-green-was-my-valley-1941#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 13:42:02 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/F9BACD5741DB53108E9CF685399E14CDA8AF49C5" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Going My Way (1944)</title>
    <description>Youthful Father Chuck O'Malley led a colorful life of sports, song, and romance before joining the Roman Catholic clergy, but his level gaze and twinkling eyes make it clear that he knows he made the right choice. After joining a parish, O'Malley's worldly knowledge helps him connect with a gang of kids looking for direction and handle the business details of the church-building fund, winning over his aging, conventional superior, Father Fitzgibbon.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/going-my-way-1944</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/going-my-way-1944#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 08:15:55 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/79027EDA8A2E1273B8CBCF538D62DB0C6151C396" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gone with the Wind (1939)</title>
    <description>Scarlett is a woman who can deal with a nation at war, Atlanta burning, the Union Army carrying off everything from her beloved Tara, the carpetbaggers who arrive after the war. Scarlett is beautiful. She has vitality. But Ashley, the man she has wanted for so long, is going to marry his placid cousin, Melanie. Mammy warns Scarlett to behave herself at the party at Twelve Oaks. There is a new man there that day, the day the Civil War begins. Rhett Butler. Scarlett does not know he is in the room when she pleads with Ashley to choose her instead of Melanie.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/gone-with-the-wind-1939</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/gone-with-the-wind-1939#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 17:29:19 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/1F225F957358FFEB30EFC046EC468346091278C4" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Grand Hotel (1932)</title>
    <description>Berlin's plushest, most expensive hotel is the setting where in the words of Dr. Otternschlag "People come, people go. Nothing ever happens.". The doctor is usually drunk so he missed the fact that Baron von Geigern is broke and trying to steal eccentric dancer Grusinskaya's pearls. He ends up stealing her heart instead. Powerful German businessman Preysing brow beats Kringelein, one of his company's lowly bookkeepers but it is the terminally ill Kringelein who holds all the cards in the end. Meanwhile, the Baron also steals the heart of Preysing's mistress, Flaemmchen, but she doesn't end up with either one of them in the end...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/grand-hotel-1932</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/grand-hotel-1932#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 03:19:30 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/679085B3986C4812937B53CA52BBB9E624BE2E4B" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gigi (1958)</title>
    <description>Weary of the conventions of Parisian society, a rich playboy and a youthful courtesan-in-training enjoy a platonic friendship, but it may not stay platonic for long. Gaston, the scion of a wealthy Parisian family finds emotional refuge from the superficial lifestyle of upper class Parisian 1900s society with the former mistress of his uncle and her outgoing, tomboy granddaughter, Gigi. When Gaston becomes aware that Gigi has matured into a woman, her grandmother and aunt, who have educated Gigi to be a wealthy man's mistress, urge the pair to act out their roles but love adds a surprise twist to this delightful turn-of-the 20th century Cinderella story.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/gigi-1958</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/gigi-1958#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 18:05:41 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/D06C9521005471D3F7004C35D89C01484A6895C8" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>From Here to Eternity (1953)</title>
    <description>It's 1941. Robert E. Lee Prewitt has requested Army transfer and has ended up at Schofield in Hawaii. His new captain, Dana Holmes, has heard of his boxing prowess and is keen to get him to represent the company. However, 'Prew' is adamant that he doesn't box anymore, so Captain Holmes gets his subordinates to make his life a living hell. Meanwhile Sergeant Warden starts seeing the captain's wife, who has a history of seeking external relief from a troubled marriage. Prew's friend Maggio has a few altercations with the sadistic stockade Sergeant 'Fatso' Judson, and Prew begins falling in love with social club employee Lorene. Unbeknownst to anyone, the Japanese bombing of Pearl Harbor looms in the distance.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/from-here-to-eternity-1953</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/from-here-to-eternity-1953#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 15:13:23 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/FDEAD642C9B26161E6D17FC195AFED54439C7B2D" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Best Years of Our Lives (1946)</title>
    <description>The story concentrates on the social re-adjustment of three World War II servicemen, each from a different station of society. Al Stephenson returns to an influential banking position, but finds it hard to reconcile his loyalties to ex-servicemen with new commercial realities. Fred Derry is an ordinary working man who finds it difficult to hold down a job or pick up the threads of his marriage. Having had both hands burnt off during the war, Homer Parrish is unsure that his fiancée's feelings are still those of love and not those of pity. Each of the veterans faces a crisis upon his arrival, and each crisis is a microcosm of the experiences of many American warriors who found an alien world awaiting them when they came marching home.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-best-years-of-our-lives-1946</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-best-years-of-our-lives-1946#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 02:26:16 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/8564C4D0138932AB226F35CCFF5149A919B13069" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ben-Hur (1959)</title>
    <description>Judah Ben-Hur lives as a rich Jewish prince and merchant in Jerusalem at the beginning of the 1st century. Together with the new governor his old friend Messala arrives as commanding officer of the Roman legions. At first they are happy to meet after a long time but their different politic views separate them. During the welcome parade a roof tile falls down from Judah's house and injures the governor. Although Messala knows they are not guilty, he sends Judah to the galleys and throws his mother and sister into prison. But Judah swears to come back and take revenge.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/ben-hur-1959</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/ben-hur-1959#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 12:01:00 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/707DEE19B1E06338CB9DAE41076E125A3B49CF77" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Bridge on the River Kwai (1957)</title>
    <description>During WW II, allied POWs in a Japanese internment camp are ordered to build a bridge to accommodate the Burma-Siam railway. Their instinct is to sabotage the bridge, but under the leadership of Colonel Nicholson they're persuaded the bridge should be built to help morale, spirit. At first, the prisoners admire Nicholson when he bravely endures torture rather than compromise his principles for the benefit of Japanese Commandant Colonel Saito, but soon they realise it's a monument to Nicholson, himself, as well as a form of collaboration with the enemy.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-bridge-on-the-river-kwai-1957</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-bridge-on-the-river-kwai-1957#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:12:36 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/830CE58F85D93AAC2566D5DA8B5FA3B121923683" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Around the World in 80 Days (1956)</title>
    <description>When this movie is made in 1956, one could circumnavigate the globe in a little less than two days. When Jules Verne wrote the story "Around the World in Eighty Days" in 1872, he predicted that one day man could accomplish the task in eighty hours, but which most considered folly to do in eighty days in current times, that is except for people like Englishman Phileas Fogg, a regimented man who believed all it would take is exacting work, the skills he possesses. He just has to make sure a train's schedule meets the required sailing schedule which meets the required coach schedule and so on. As such, he takes up what ends up being the highly publicized twenty thousand pounds sterling wager from his fellow members at the London Reform Club to do so, losing the bet which would ruin him financially. Along for the ride is Fogg's new, loyal and devoted valet, the recently arrived Latin immigrant, Passepartout, who possesses unusual skills which could be major assets, but whose all consuming...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/around-the-world-in-80-days-1956</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/around-the-world-in-80-days-1956#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 06:40:16 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/684C4721E1D15A172E39C1596955BC4914AF8055" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Apartment (1960)</title>
    <description>As of November 1, 1959, mild mannered C.C. Baxter has been working at Consolidated Life, an insurance company, for close to four years, and is one of close to thirty-two thousand employees located in their Manhattan head office. To distinguish himself from all the other lowly cogs in the company in the hopes of moving up the corporate ladder, he often works late, but only because he can't get into his apartment, located off of Central Park West, since he has provided it to a handful of company executives - Mssrs. Dobisch, Kirkeby, Vanderhoff and Eichelberger - on a rotating basis for their extramarital liaisons in return for a good word to the personnel director, Jeff D. Sheldrake. When Baxter is called into Sheldrake's office for the first time, he learns that it isn't just to be promoted as he expects, but also to add married Sheldrake to the list to who he will lend his apartment. Dobisch, Kirkeby, Vanderhoff and Eichelberger are now feeling neglected as Baxter no longer needs ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-apartment-1960</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-apartment-1960#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 23:55:45 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/CC11A7D6F130352919B85CF37563B7B867DF9911" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>An American in Paris (1951)</title>
    <description>Jerry Mulligan, a struggling American painter in Paris, is "discovered" by an influential heiress with an interest in more than Jerry's art. Jerry in turn falls for Lise, a young French girl already engaged to a cabaret singer. Jerry jokes, sings and dances with his best friend, an acerbic would-be concert pianist, while romantic complications abound.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/an-american-in-paris-1951</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/an-american-in-paris-1951#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 02:04:27 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/A9CEF0B822F8638E63A0EDCAA672C7314EB2427F" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>All About Eve (1950)</title>
    <description>Eve Harrington (Anne Baxter) is waiting backstage to meet her idol, talented but aging Broadway star Margo Channing (Bette Davis). It seems innocent enough as Eve explains that she has seen Margo in EVERY performance of her current play. Margo and her friends take Eve under their wing but only theatre critic Addison DeWitt (George Sanders) sees through Eve's evil plan, which is to take Margo's parts and her fiancé, Bill Simpson (Gary Merrill) too.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/all-about-eve-1950</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/all-about-eve-1950#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 06:20:59 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/979DD4160768C36228C50F76498C85335C2A56AD" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Sound of Music (1965)</title>
    <description>In 1930's Austria, a young woman named Maria (Dame Julie Andrews) is failing miserably in her attempts to become a nun. When Navy Captain Georg Von Trapp (Christopher Plummer) writes to the convent asking for a governess that can handle his seven mischievous children, Maria is given the job. The Captain's wife is dead, and he is often away, and runs the household as strictly as he does the ships he sails on. The children are unhappy and resentful of the governesses that their father keeps hiring, and have managed to run each of them off one by one. When Maria arrives, she is initially met with the same hostility, but her kindness, understanding, and sense of fun soon draws them to her and brings some much-needed joy into all their lives - including the Captain's. Eventually he and Maria find themselves falling in love, even though Georg is already engaged to a Baroness and Maria is still a postulant. The romance makes them both start questioning the decisions they have made. Their ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-sound-of-music-1965</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-sound-of-music-1965#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 03:22:21 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/1E317E6277048CBB07836C9FD6E175CF64FC94FC" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>All Quiet on the Western Front (1930)</title>
    <description>This is an English language film (made in America) adapted from a novel by German author Erich Maria Remarque. The film follows a group of German schoolboys, talked into enlisting at the beginning of World War 1 by their jingoistic teacher. The story is told entirely through the experiences of the young German recruits and highlights the tragedy of war through the eyes of individuals. As the boys witness death and mutilation all around them, any preconceptions about "the enemy" and the "rights and wrongs" of the conflict disappear, leaving them angry and bewildered. This is highlighted in the scene where Paul mortally wounds a French soldier and then weeps bitterly as he fights to save his life while trapped in a shell crater with the body. The film is not about heroism but about drudgery and futility and the gulf between the concept of war and the actuality.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/all-quiet-on-the-western-front-1930</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/all-quiet-on-the-western-front-1930#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 02:12:34 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/E83F700D82316D1BEE8DE6EDEF5DD6D8F5A4C3AE" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>A Man for All Seasons (1966)</title>
    <description>The story takes place in sixteenth century England. But men like Sir Thomas More, who love life yet have the moral fiber to lay down their lives for their principles, are found in every century. Concentrating on the last seven years of the English Chancellor's life, the struggle between More and King Henry VIII hinges on Henry's determination to break with Rome so he can divorce his current wife and wed again, and good Catholic More's inability to go along with such heresy. More resigns as Chancellor, hoping to be able to live out his life as a private citizen. But Henry will settle for nothing less than that the much respected More give public approval to his headstrong course.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/a-man-for-all-seasons-1966</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/a-man-for-all-seasons-1966#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 21:00:43 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/C737276E0A650091C9FFA30524AFB7573315AF91" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>In the Heat of the Night (1967)</title>
    <description>Detective Virgil Tibbs is caught up in the racial tension of the US South when he is arrested after the murder of a prominent businessman. Tibbs was simply waiting for his next train at the station in Sparta, Mississippi and the confusion is soon resolved but when local police chief Gillespie learns that Tibbs is the Philadelphia PD's number one homicide expert, he reluctantly asks for his assistance. The murdered man, Mr. Colbert, had come to Sparta from the North to build a new factory and his wife and business associates immediately point the finger at Endicott, the most powerful man in the county and the one who had the most to lose if a major new employer comes to the area. Tibbs' life is clearly in danger but he perseveres in a highly charged and racially explosive environment until the killer is found.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/in-the-heat-of-the-night-1967</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/in-the-heat-of-the-night-1967#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 11:54:26 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/AE10F3F271877008DC85CE4C1453580734DD9354" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Oliver! (1968)</title>
    <description>Musical adaptation of Charles Dickens's classic tale of an orphan who runs away from the orphanage and hooks up with a group of boys trained to be pickpockets by an elderly mentor.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/oliver-1968</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/oliver-1968#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 18:29:47 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/A26984686D700B05DDD51D0A9ED6D04261BC70C7" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Midnight Cowboy (1969)</title>
    <description>Texas greenhorn Joe Buck arrives in New York City for the first time. Preening himself as a real "hustler", he finds that he is the one getting "hustled" until he teams up with down-and-out but resilient outcast Ratso Rizzo. The initial "country cousin meets city cousin" relationship deepens. In their efforts to bilk a hostile world rebuffing them at every turn, this unlikely pair progress from partners in shady business to comrades. Each has found his first real friend.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/midnight-cowboy-1969</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/midnight-cowboy-1969#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 14:02:34 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/C01D22593B5E8FF86D182809030428438BE4516B" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The French Connection (1971)</title>
    <description>William Friedkin's gritty police drama portrays two tough New York City cops trying to intercept a huge heroin shipment coming from France. An interesting contrast is established between 'Popeye' Doyle, a short-tempered alcoholic bigot who is nevertheless a hard-working and dedicated police officer, and his nemesis Alain Charnier, a suave and urbane gentleman who is nevertheless a criminal and one of the largest drug suppliers of pure heroin to North America. During the surveillance and eventual bust, Friedkin provides one of the most gripping and memorable car chase sequences ever filmed.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-french-connection-1971</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-french-connection-1971#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:34:19 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/B97F9239653E4EF47DB896D8BFE498B4C4769ACB" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Patton (1970)</title>
    <description>"Patton" tells the tale of General George S. Patton, famous tank commander of World War II. The film begins with Patton's career in North Africa and progresses through the invasion of Europe and the fall of the Third Reich. Side plots also speak of Patton's numerous faults such his temper and tendency toward insubordination, faults that would prevent him from becoming the lead American general in the Normandy Invasion as well as to his being relieved as Occupation Commander of Germany.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/patton-1970</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/patton-1970#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:23:12 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/E217B7449C1B913526A55B25CB9DDA338D2C6A63" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Godfather (1972)</title>
    <description>The Godfather "Don" Vito Corleone is the head of the Corleone mafia family in New York. He is at the event of his daughter's wedding. Michael, Vito's youngest son and a decorated WW II Marine is also present at the wedding. Michael seems to be uninterested in being a part of the family business. Vito is a powerful man, and is kind to all those who give him respect but is ruthless against those who do not. But when a powerful and treacherous rival wants to sell drugs and needs the Don's influence for the same, Vito refuses to do it. What follows is a clash between Vito's fading old values and the new ways which may cause Michael to do the thing he was most reluctant in doing and wage a mob war against all the other mafia families which could tear the Corleone family apart.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-godfather-1972</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-godfather-1972#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:36:37 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/5E915039C619366E490D08DB3FFED21F3A3AE84A" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Godfather: Part II (1974)</title>
    <description>The continuing saga of the Corleone crime family tells the story of a young Vito Corleone growing up in Sicily and in 1910s New York; and follows Michael Corleone in the 1950s as he attempts to expand the family business into Las Vegas, Hollywood and Cuba.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-godfather-part-ii-1974</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-godfather-part-ii-1974#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:36:45 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/6C9124FE9A99B2001FAD76A76152691BC515A80D" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (1975)</title>
    <description>McMurphy has a criminal past and has once again gotten himself into trouble and is sentenced by the court. To escape labor duties in prison, McMurphy pleads insanity and is sent to a ward for the mentally unstable. Once here, McMurphy both endures and stands witness to the abuse and degradation of the oppressive Nurse Ratched, who gains superiority and power through the flaws of the other inmates. McMurphy and the other inmates band together to make a rebellious stance against the atrocious Nurse.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/one-flew-over-the-cuckoos-nest-1975</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/one-flew-over-the-cuckoos-nest-1975#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:30:32 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/BFF25FBBAC88B6B9D24DBC18B359734015C8ABF4" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Sting (1973)</title>
    <description>Johnny Hooker, a small time grifter, unknowingly steals from Doyle Lonnegan, a big time crime boss, when he pulls a standard street con. Lonnegan demands satisfaction for the insult. After his partner, Luther, is killed, Hooker flees, and seeks the help of Henry Gondorff, one of Luther's contacts, who is a master of the long con. Hooker wants to use Gondorff's expertise to take Lonnegan for an enormous sum of money to even the score, since he admits he "doesn't know enough about killing to kill him." They devise a complicated scheme and amass a talented group of other con artists who want their share of the reparations. The stakes are high in this game, and our heroes must not only deal with Lonnegan's murderous tendencies, but also other side players who want a piece of the action. To win, Hooker and Gondorff will need all their skills...and a fair amount of confidence.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-sting-1973</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-sting-1973#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 11:42:00 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/8ADA16FF0609FA279B5C66E7BE8937E4D213E975" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Rocky (1976)</title>
    <description>Rocky Balboa is a struggling boxer trying to make the big time, working as a debt collector for a pittance. When heavyweight champion Apollo Creed visits Philadelphia, his managers want to set up an exhibition match between Creed and a struggling boxer, touting the fight as a chance for a "nobody" to become a "somebody". The match is supposed to be easily won by Creed, but someone forgot to tell Rocky, who sees this as his only shot at the big time.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/rocky-1976</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/rocky-1976#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:07:52 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/CCE385B2472097275F5E56D500CC80D65712856B" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Annie Hall (1977)</title>
    <description>Alvy Singer, a forty year old twice divorced, neurotic, intellectual Jewish New York stand-up comic, reflects on the demise of his latest relationship, to Annie Hall, an insecure, flighty, Midwestern WASP aspiring nightclub singer. Unlike his previous relationships, Alvy believed he may have worked out all the issues in his life through fifteen years of therapy to make this relationship with Annie last, among those issues being not wanting to date any woman that would want to date him, and thus subconsciously pushing those women away. Alvy not only reviews the many ups and many downs of their relationship, but also reviews the many facets of his makeup that led to him starting to date Annie. Those facets include growing up next to Coney Island in Brooklyn, being attracted to the opposite sex for as long as he can remember, and enduring years of Jewish guilt with his constantly arguing parents.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/annie-hall-1977</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/annie-hall-1977#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 21:29:23 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/F5AC61D1ED17193F9B2AF32CC7907D2E624D3163" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Deer Hunter (1978)</title>
    <description>Michael, Steven and Nicky are 3 best friends who enjoy going Deer hunting quote often. These men get enlisted to head to Vietnam to fight for their country and celebrate with a farewell party, as well as Nicky marrying a pregnant woman named "Angela." After the horrors during the war and edge-grabbing games of Russian Roulette that these men are forced to play, Michael returns home and realizes that his Deer hunting outings aren't the same as they used to be, because of the war and he eventually finds out that Steven is handicapped and Nicky hasn't returned from Vietnam, and in response, he heads back to Vietnam to rescue him.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-deer-hunter-1978</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-deer-hunter-1978#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:22:04 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/897BD6E50BF2179BB8A700B0C23D34DE405F0A74" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Kramer vs. Kramer (1979)</title>
    <description>Ted Kramer is a career man for whom his work comes before his family. His wife Joanna cannot take this anymore, so she decides to leave him. Ted is now faced with the tasks of housekeeping and taking care of himself and their young son Billy. When he has learned to adjust his life to these new responsibilities, Joanna resurfaces and wants Billy back. Ted, however, refuses to give him up, so they go to court to fight for the custody of their son.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/kramer-vs-kramer-1979</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/kramer-vs-kramer-1979#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:37:48 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/E4C56DE1C18C7E458AD9866F76F488D8868CB93A" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ordinary People (1980)</title>
    <description>Beth, Calvin, and their son Conrad are living in the aftermath of the death of the other son. Conrad is overcome by grief and misplaced guilt to the extent of a suicide attempt. He is in therapy. Beth had always preferred his brother and is having difficulty being supportive to Conrad. Calvin is trapped between the two trying to hold the family together.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/ordinary-people-1980</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/ordinary-people-1980#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 23:13:30 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/7B5AABD72BB37DA02AB46FE7CF4252F9A3F6FB48" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Chariots of Fire (1981)</title>
    <description>It's the post-World War I era. Britons Harold Abrahams and Eric Liddell are both naturally gifted fast sprinters, but approach running and how it fits into their respective lives differently. The son of a Lithuanian Jew, Harold, who lives a somewhat privileged life as a student at Cambridge, uses being the fastest to overcome what he sees as the obstacles he faces in life as a Jew despite that privilege. In his words to paraphrase an old adage, he is often invited to the trough, but isn't allowed to drink. His running prowess does earn him the respect of his classmates, especially his running teammates, and to some extent the school administration, if only he maintains what they consider proper gentlemanly decorum, which isn't always the case in their minds. Born in China, the son of Christian missionaries, Eric, a Scot, is a devout member of the Church of Scotland who eventually wants to return to that missionary work. He sees running as a win-win in that the notoriety of being fast ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/chariots-of-fire-1981</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/chariots-of-fire-1981#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 22:23:11 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/F8043ABE81EA5749370AB1235884CEC50AE5390C" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gandhi (1982)</title>
    <description>In 1893, Mohandas K. Gandhi is thrown off a South African train for being an Indian and traveling in a first class compartment. Gandhi realizes that the laws are biased against Indians and decides to start a non-violent protest campaign for the rights of all Indians in South Africa. After numerous arrests and the unwanted attention of the world, the government finally relents by recognizing rights for Indians, though not for the native blacks of South Africa. After this victory, Gandhi is invited back to India, where he is now considered something of a national hero. He is urged to take up the fight for India's independence from the British Empire. Gandhi agrees, and mounts a non-violent non-cooperation campaign of unprecedented scale, coordinating millions of Indians nationwide. There are some setbacks, such as violence against the protesters and Gandhi's occasional imprisonment. Nevertheless, the campaign generates great attention, and Britain faces intense public pressure. Too weak...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/gandhi-1982</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/gandhi-1982#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 23:37:03 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/E20874383BB4552783791DDA9C4BBDA6DA651D55" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Terms of Endearment (1983)</title>
    <description>Aurora and Emma are mother and daughter who march to different drummers. Beginning with Emma's marriage, Aurora shows how difficult and loving she can be. The movie covers several years of their lives as each finds different reasons to go on living and find joy. Aurora's interludes with Garrett Breedlove, retired astronaut and next door neighbor are quite striking. In the end, different people show their love in very different ways.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/terms-of-endearment-1983</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/terms-of-endearment-1983#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 10:36:16 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/E4FBD4CD711E7D75F17C62849361A41D7EBE51B3" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Amadeus (1984)</title>
    <description>Antonio Salieri believes that Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's music is divine and miraculous. He wishes he was himself as good a musician as Mozart so that he can praise the Lord through composing. He began his career as a devout man who believes his success and talent as a composer are God's rewards for his piety. He's also content as the respected, financially well-off, court composer of Austrian Emperor Joseph II. But he's shocked to learn that Mozart is such a vulgar creature, and can't understand why God favored Mozart to be his instrument. Salieri's envy has made him an enemy of God whose greatness was evident in Mozart. He is ready to take revenge against God and Mozart for his own musical mediocrity.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/amadeus-1984</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/amadeus-1984#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 21:21:53 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/44D7360363E5BE623CF0D0D83ADF86AB2E8FC46C" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Rain Man (1988)</title>
    <description>Charles Sanford "Charlie" Babbit is a self-centered Los Angeles-based automobile dealer/hustler/bookie who is at war with his own life. Charlie, as a young teenager, used his father's 1949 Buick convertible without permission and as a result, he went to jail for two days on account that his father reported it stolen. It is then that Charlie learns that his estranged father died and left him from his last will and testament a huge bed of roses and the car while the remainder will of $3 Million goes into a trust fund to be distributed to someone. Charlie seemed pretty angry by this and decides to look into this matter. It seems as if that "someone" is Raymond, Charlie's unknown brother, an autistic savant who lives in a world of his own, resides at the Walbrook Institute. Charlie then kidnaps Raymond and decides to take him on a lust for life trip to the west coast as a threat to get the $3 Million inheritance. Raymond's acts and nagging, including repeated talks of "Abbott &amp; Costello",...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/rain-man-1988</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/rain-man-1988#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:54:51 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/CFBAA1B40A7A4F5AAC57B10BB8FDACADA197E111" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Platoon (1986)</title>
    <description>Chris Taylor is a young, naive American who gives up college and volunteers for combat in Vietnam. Upon arrival, he quickly discovers that his presence is quite nonessential, and is considered insignificant to the other soldiers, as he has not fought for as long as the rest of them and felt the effects of combat. Chris has two non-commissioned officers, the ill-tempered and indestructible Staff Sergeant Robert Barnes and the more pleasant and cooperative Sergeant Elias Grodin. A line is drawn between the two NCOs and a number of men in the platoon when an illegal killing occurs during a village raid. As the war continues, Chris himself draws towards psychological meltdown. And as he struggles for survival, he soon realizes he is fighting two battles, the conflict with the enemy and the conflict between the men within his platoon.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/platoon-1986</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/platoon-1986#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:45:09 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/0B4A63C5807F8B625A36A39E0F672F1B9B352BEE" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Out of Africa (1985)</title>
    <description>Follows the life of Karen Blixen, who establishes a plantation in Africa. Her life is Complicated by a husband of convenience (Bror Blixen), a true love (Denys), troubles on the plantation, schooling of the natives, war, and catching VD from her husband.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/out-of-africa-1985</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/out-of-africa-1985#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 06:18:39 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/36B3C3081CC5CF85148AB6D979269D22ED8E3EF7" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Last Emperor (1987)</title>
    <description>This sweeping account of the life of Pu-Yi, the last emperor of China, follows the leader's tumultuous reign. After being captured by the Red Army as a war criminal in 1950, Pu-Yi recalls his childhood from prison. He remembers his lavish youth in the Forbidden City, where he was afforded every luxury but unfortunately sheltered from the outside world and complex political situation surrounding him. As revolution sweeps through China, the world Pu-Yi knew is dramatically upended.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-last-emperor-1987</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-last-emperor-1987#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 05:10:13 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/4EB507DA6CB6BA03189275E4450BBBA974178A4D" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Driving Miss Daisy (1989)</title>
    <description>An elderly Jewish widow living in Atlanta can no longer drive. Her son insists she allow him to hire a driver, which in the 1950s meant a black man. She resists any change in her life but, Hoke, the driver is hired by her son. She refuses to allow him to drive her anywhere at first, but Hoke slowly wins her over with his native good graces. The movie is directly taken from a stage play and does show it. It covers over twenty years of the pair's life together as they slowly build a relationship that transcends their differences.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/driving-miss-daisy-1989</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/driving-miss-daisy-1989#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 23:08:33 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/D512FA6EC453E25CAF67C530395E494EA564AA85" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Silence of the Lambs (1991)</title>
    <description>F.B.I. trainee Clarice Starling (Jodie Foster) works hard to advance her career, while trying to hide or put behind her West Virginia roots, of which if some knew, would automatically classify her as being backward or white trash. After graduation, she aspires to work in the agency's Behavioral Science Unit under the leadership of Jack Crawford (Scott Glenn). While she is still a trainee, Crawford asks her to question Dr. Hannibal Lecter (Sir Anthony Hopkins), a psychiatrist imprisoned, thus far, for eight years in maximum security isolation for being a serial killer who cannibalized his victims. Clarice is able to figure out the assignment is to pick Lecter's brains to help them solve another serial murder case, that of someone coined by the media as "Buffalo Bill" (Ted Levine), who has so far killed five victims, all located in the eastern U.S., all young women, who are slightly overweight (especially around the hips), all who were drowned in natural bodies of water, and all who ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-silence-of-the-lambs-1991</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-silence-of-the-lambs-1991#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 03:20:46 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/B6EC2A4507B13ADE6BC4A1FAC5B39CA25888B326" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Unforgiven (1992)</title>
    <description>After escaping death by the skin of her teeth, the horribly disfigured prostitute, Delilah Fitzgerald, and her appalled and equally furious co-workers summon up the courage to seek retribution in 1880s Wyoming's dangerous town of Big Whiskey. With a hefty bounty on the perpetrators' heads, triggered by the tough Sheriff "Little Bill" Daggett's insufficient sense of justice, the infamous former outlaw and now destitute Kansas hog farmer, William Munny, embarks on a murderous last mission to find the men behind the hideous crime. Along with his old partner-in-crime, Ned Logan, and the brash but inexperienced young gunman, the "Schofield Kid", Munny enters a perilous world he has renounced many years ago, knowing that he walks right into a deadly trap; however, he still needs to find a way to raise his motherless children. Now, blood demands blood. Who is the hero, and who is the villain?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/unforgiven-1992</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/unforgiven-1992#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 03:54:57 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/82529944B6EBE1C74D70D39C451A5BFB65071334" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Dances with Wolves (1990)</title>
    <description>Lt. John Dunbar is dubbed a hero after he accidentally leads Union troops to a victory during the Civil War. He requests a position on the western frontier, but finds it deserted. He soon finds out he is not alone, but meets a wolf he dubs "Two-socks" and a curious Indian tribe. Dunbar quickly makes friends with the tribe, and discovers a white woman who was raised by the Indians. He gradually earns the respect of these native people, and sheds his white-man's ways.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/dances-with-wolves-1990</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/dances-with-wolves-1990#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 22:43:28 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/6E71BF70CBB5AAFC230A9CB8BD9FF594A0B94B83" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Braveheart (1995)</title>
    <description>William Wallace is a Scottish rebel who leads an uprising against the cruel English ruler Edward the Longshanks, who wishes to inherit the crown of Scotland for himself. When he was a young boy, William Wallace's father and brother, along with many others, lost their lives trying to free Scotland. Once he loses another of his loved ones, William Wallace begins his long quest to make Scotland free once and for all, along with the assistance of Robert the Bruce.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/braveheart-1995</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/braveheart-1995#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 22:11:03 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/125E66ECD5346CBDBD7AAE72BEF93651712877A9" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The English Patient (1996)</title>
    <description>October 1944 in war torn Italy. Hana (Juliette Binoche), a French-Canadian nurse working in a mobile army medical unit, feels like everything she loves in life dies on her. Because of the difficulty traveling and the dangers, especially as the landscape is still heavily booby-trapped with mines, Hana volunteers to stay behind at a church to care solely for a dying semi-amnesiac patient, who is badly burned and disfigured. She agrees to catch up to the rest of the unit after he dies. All the patient remembers is that he is English, and that he is married. Their solitude is disrupted with the arrival at the church of fellow Canadian David Caravaggio (Willem Dafoe), part of the Intelligence Service, who is certain that he knows the patient as a man who cooperated with the Germans. Caravaggio believes that the patient's memory is largely intact, and that he is running away from his past, in part, or in its entirety. The patient does open up about his past, all surrounding his work as a ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-english-patient-1996</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-english-patient-1996#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:27:05 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/F5DA33E2A18EC56542DFA706342151EDD0761C6D" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Titanic (1997)</title>
    <description>84 years later, a 100 year-old woman named Rose DeWitt Bukater tells the story to her granddaughter Lizzy Calvert, Brock Lovett, Lewis Bodine, Bobby Buell and Anatoly Mikailavich on the Keldysh about her life set in April 10th 1912, on a ship called Titanic when young Rose boards the departing ship with the upper-class passengers and her mother, Ruth DeWitt Bukater, and her fiancé, Caledon Hockley. Meanwhile, a drifter and artist named Jack Dawson and his best friend Fabrizio De Rossi win third-class tickets to the ship in a game. And she explains the whole story from departure until the death of Titanic on its first and last voyage April 15th, 1912 at 2:20 in the morning.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/titanic-1997</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/titanic-1997#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 19:25:11 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/98CD5D90252265F1C59AB47330FF4C39F48CCC78" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Shakespeare in Love (1998)</title>
    <description>William Shakespeare (Joseph Fiennes) is a known but struggling poet, playwright, and actor, who not only has sold his next play to both Philip Henslowe (Geoffrey Rush) and Richard Burbage (Martin Clunes), but now faces a far more difficult problem: he is bereft of ideas and has yet to begin writing. He is in search of his muse, the woman who will inspire him but all attempts fail him until he meets the beautiful Viola De Lesseps (Gwyneth Paltrow). She loves the theatre and would like nothing more than to take to the stage, but is forbidden from doing so as only men can be actors. She is also a great admirer of Shakespeare's works. Dressing as a man, and going by the name of "Thomas Kent", she auditions and is ideal for a part in his next play. Shakespeare soon sees through her disguise and they begin a love affair, one they know cannot end happily for them as he is already married and she has been promised to the dour Lord Wessex (Colin Firth). As the company rehearses his new play, ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/shakespeare-in-love-1998</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/shakespeare-in-love-1998#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:21:39 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/2B09DF75480507453A56D86629AAC3687CB8596E" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>American Beauty (1999)</title>
    <description>After his death sometime in his forty-third year, suburbanite Lester Burnham tells of the last few weeks of his life, during which he had no idea of his imminent passing. He is a husband to real estate agent Carolyn Burnham and father to high school student Janie Burnham. Although Lester and Carolyn once loved each other, they now merely tolerate each other. Typical wallflower Janie too hates both her parents, the three who suffer individually in silence in their home life. Janie tries to steer clear of both her parents. Carolyn, relatively new to the real estate business, wants to create the persona of success to further her career, she aspiring to the professional life of Buddy Kane, the king of the real estate business in their neighborhood. Lester merely walks mindlessly through life, including at his job in advertising. His company is downsizing, and he, like all the other employees, has to justify his position to the newly hired efficiency expert to keep his job. Things change ...</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/american-beauty-1999</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/american-beauty-1999#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 21:22:23 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/783FE3217B56242360448767CCD3967D209556B3" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>A Beautiful Mind (2001)</title>
    <description>From the heights of notoriety to the depths of depravity, John Forbes Nash, Jr. experienced it all. A mathematical genius, he made an astonishing discovery early in his career and stood on the brink of international acclaim. But the handsome and arrogant Nash soon found himself on a painful and harrowing journey of self-discovery. After many years of struggle, he eventually triumphed over his tragedy, and finally - late in life - received the Nobel Prize.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/a-beautiful-mind-2001</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/a-beautiful-mind-2001#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 20:55:49 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/9CA50DA836B52A6BCB06AAA91BB2478FD96F5DD0" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gladiator (2000)</title>
    <description>Maximus is a powerful Roman general, loved by the people and the aging Emperor, Marcus Aurelius. Before his death, the Emperor chooses Maximus to be his heir over his own son, Commodus, and a power struggle leaves Maximus and his family condemned to death. The powerful general is unable to save his family, and his loss of will allows him to get captured and put into the Gladiator games until he dies. The only desire that fuels him now is the chance to rise to the top so that he will be able to look into the eyes of the man who will feel his revenge.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/gladiator-2000</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/gladiator-2000#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 23:40:53 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/9BFAB920305925F9954D8C4B9DEDCD4C6B12FFEA" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Chicago (2002)</title>
    <description>Murderesses Velma Kelly (Catherine Zeta-Jones) (a chanteuse and tease who killed her husband and sister after finding them in bed together) and Roxie Hart (Renée Zellweger) (who killed her boyfriend when she discovered he wasn't going to make her a star) find themselves on death row together and fight for the fame that will keep them from the gallows in 1920s Chicago.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/chicago-2002</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/chicago-2002#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 22:25:11 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/F86DE694E9011D927719C6EF0DF7012BBB1A5E62" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King (2003)</title>
    <description>The final confrontation between the forces of good and evil fighting for control of the future of Middle-earth. Frodo and Sam reach Mordor in their quest to destroy the One Ring, while Aragorn leads the forces of good against Sauron's evil army at the stone city of Minas Tirith.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-2003</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-2003#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:58:16 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/AD73D5576DC4ECFEEA4353D4503F9B3F93DFA740" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Million Dollar Baby (2004)</title>
    <description>Wanting to learn from the best, aspiring boxer Maggie Fitzgerald (Hilary Swank) wants Frankie Dunn (Clint Eastwood) to train her. At the outset, he flatly refuses saying he has no interest in training a girl. Frankie leads a lonely existence, alienated from his only daughter and having few friends. Maggie's rough around the edges, but shows a lot of grit in the ring and he eventually relents. Maggie not only proves to be the boxer he always dreamed of having under his wing, but a friend who fills the great void he's had in his life. Maggie's career skyrockets, but an accident in the ring leads her to ask Frankie for one last favor.</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/million-dollar-baby-2004</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/million-dollar-baby-2004#720p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:09:08 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/519C7A33678252D75BF05CCDCDE5AB3AF0DE621C" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Departed (2006)</title>
    <description>In this crime-action tour de force, the South Boston state police force is waging war on Irish-American organized crime. Young undercover cop Billy Costigan is assigned to infiltrate the mob syndicate run by gangland chief Frank Costello. While Billy quickly gains Costello's confidence, Colin Sullivan, a hardened young criminal who has infiltrated the state police as an informer for the syndicate is rising to a position of power in the Special Investigation Unit. Each man becomes deeply consumed by their double lives, gathering information about the plans and counter-plans of the operations they have penetrated. But when it becomes clear to both the mob and the police that there is a mole in their midst, Billy and Colin are suddenly in danger of being caught and exposed to the enemy - and each must race to uncover the identity of the other man in time to save themselves. But is either willing to turn on their friends and comrades they've made during their long stints undercover?</description>
    <link>https://yts.mx/movies/the-departed-2006</link>
    <guid>https://yts.mx/movies/the-departed-2006#1080p</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 02:22:18 -0000</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://yts.mx/torrent/download/6B4C0A61376C4DD7E3BC2E5EE543B3BBB3282ECD" type="application/x-bittorrent"></enclosure>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>